(Sheldon:)It's not a present.
It's the present.
(Sheldon:)Look, there's you and me.
It's Penny and Amy.
(Sheldon:)We're playing Pictionary, in the present.
(Penny:)Oh, my God, we're gonna kill them.
- It's a quark-gluon plasma.
- No.
(Sheldon:)It's asymptotically free partons
inside a quark-gluon plasma.
(Leonard:)Nothing with quarks.
(Sheldon:)It's an observational rebuttal
of the Lambda-CDM model of the universe.
(Sheldon:)- No.
- It's a chocolate chip cookie!
Yes!
- How could you miss that?
- Hey!
(Sheldon:)If you want someone to guess
chocolate chip cookie...
(Sheldon:)...you draw a glass of milk next to it.
- Penny got it.
- Yeah, only after I eliminated...
(Sheldon:)...all the obvious answers.
(Sheldon:)You're welcome.